<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
	<id>
		com.heroicgameslauncher.hgl
	</id>
	<name>
		Heroic Games Launcher
	</name>
	<summary>
		An Open Source GOG and Epic Games Launcher.
	</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="de">
		Ein Open Source Spielelauncher for GOG und Epic Games
	</summary>
	<url type="homepage">
		https://heroicgameslauncher.com
	</url>
	<url type="bugtracker">
		https://github.com/Heroic-Games-Launcher/HeroicGamesLauncher/issues
	</url>
	<url type="donation">
		https://ko-fi.com/heroicgames
	</url>
	<url type="translate">
		https://hosted.weblate.org/projects/heroic-games-launcher
	</url>
	<url type="help">
		https://github.com/Heroic-Games-Launcher/HeroicGamesLauncher/wiki
	</url>
	<url type="vcs-browser">
		https://github.com/Heroic-Games-Launcher/HeroicGamesLauncher
	</url>
	<metadata_license>
		CC0-1.0
	</metadata_license>
	<project_license>
		GPL-3.0
	</project_license>
	<description>
		<p>
			Heroic is an Open Source Games Launcher. It supports launching games from the Epic Games Store using Legendary, GOG Games and Amazon Prime games using GOGDL and Nile respectively.
		</p>
		<p xml:lang="de">
			Heroic ist ein Open Source Spielelauncher. Er unterstützt das Starten von Spielen aus dem Epic Games Store mit Legendary, GOG Spielen und Amazon Prime Spielen mit GOGDL und Nile.
		</p>
		<p>
			Main Features:
		</p>
		<p xml:lang="de">
			Hauptfeatures:
		</p>
		<ul>
			<li>
				Have access to your Epic, Amazon and GOG games in a intuitive interface.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Zugriff auf deine Spielebibliothek von Epic Games, Amazon und GOG durch eine intuitive Benutzeroberfläche.
			</li>
			<li>
				Add Games your own games native or not.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Du kannst deine eigenen Spiele hinzufügen, egal ob nativ oder nicht.
			</li>
			<li>
				A Download queue to download multiple games at once.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Eine Download-Warteschlange, um mehrere Spiele gleichzeitig herunterzuladen.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Zugriff auf deine Spielebibliothek von Epic Games und GOG durch eine intuitive Benutzeroberfläche.
			</li>
			<li>
				Install and launch your Windows Games using Wine or Proton. Or Launch your Native GOG Games.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Windows Spiele könne mithilfe von Wine oder Proton gestartet werden. Native Spiele von GOG können direkt gestartet werden.
			</li>
			<li>
				Cloud Saves support for the both GOG and Epic Games.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Spielstände von Epic Games können in der Cloud gespeichert werden.
			</li>
			<li>
				Import Games installed through the Epic Store or GOG Galaxy.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Installierte Spiele können aus dem Epic Games Sore oder aus GOG Galaxy importiert werden.
			</li>
			<li>
				Verify and Repair corrupted installations or even move your installation to different folders.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Installationen können auf Beschädigungen überprüft und repariert werden, sowie in andere Ordner verschoben werden.
			</li>
			<li>
				Access the games stores and also Heroic Wiki directly from the App.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Direkter Zugriff auf die Spielestores und das Heroic Wiki.
			</li>
			<li>
				Check HowLongtoBeat database to see how long it will take to finish a game.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Die HowLongtoBeat Datenbank kann genutzt werden, um zu sehen, wie lange ein Spiel dauert.
			</li>
			<li>
				And many more features
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Und viele weitere Features
			</li>
		</ul>
		<p>
			Current Limitations on the Flatpak:
		</p>
		<p xml:lang="de">
			Aktuelle Einschränkungen des Flatpaks:
		</p>
		<ul>
			<li>
				Heroic will not find or use Wine and Proton Flatpak versions. At least for now.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Heroic findet aktuell keine Wine oder Proton Versionen, die per Flatpak installiert sind
			</li>
			<li>
				For now would be better to use the Built-in Wine Manager to download and install Wine and Proton Versions.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Momentan ist es am besten, den eingebauten Wine Manager zu benutzen, um Wine und Proton Versionen zu downloaden und zu installieren.
			</li>
			<li>
				It should find Proton from the Steam folder for both Steam Flatpak and non-Flatpak if they are on installed on the library inside your $HOME folder
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Heroic sollte Proton Versionen von Steam (Nativ und Flatpak) finden, sofern sie innerhalb der Bibliothek des Benutzerordners installiert sind.
			</li>
			<li>
				Heroic cannot access /usr/bin so it won't be able to find any wine or proton isntalled there for now.
			</li>
			<li xml:lang="de">
				Heroic hat keinen Zugriff auf /usr/bin, weshalb es dort installierte Wine oder Proton Versionen nicht finden kann.
			</li>
		</ul>
	</description>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1">
		<content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">
			moderate
		</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">
			moderate
		</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="violence-realistic">
			moderate
		</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">
			moderate
		</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="money-purchasing">
			intense
		</content_attribute>
	</content_rating>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">
		com.heroicgameslauncher.hgl.desktop
	</launchable>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>
				Library Grid
			</caption>
			<image>
				https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/26871415/216277678-3e90f432-548c-43b8-8c25-79ecc86ba9d3.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>
				Settings
			</caption>
			<image>
				https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/26871415/216277779-16b20fa1-77fe-4560-aabe-d2d6e5cf8554.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>
				Game Screen
			</caption>
			<image>
				https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/26871415/216277885-7365d5ee-5a56-4c14-9ff2-12f8243cf5dc.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>
				Downloads Screen
			</caption>
			<image>
				https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/26871415/216278264-2cf4b170-f315-443d-98ac-1a34873113fe.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>
				Stores
			</caption>
			<image>
				https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/26871415/184144277-699e1108-52d9-4558-b113-84db5c90922c.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>
				Library List
			</caption>
			<image>
				https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/26871415/184139791-8666bc1d-a54f-467c-8c30-ea1eb6d24458.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>
				Game Page Not Installed
			</caption>
			<image>
				https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/26871415/216278656-05f6e654-7a9b-403c-9aa6-9e020c4c6d90.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<releases>
		<release version="v2.9.0" date="2023-07-24">
			<description>
				<p>
					General
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Amazon Prime Gaming support
					</li>
					<li>
						Adapt layout properly to RTL languages
					</li>
					<li>
						Provide Protondb information on game page
					</li>
					<li>
						Post playtime to gameplay.gog.com
					</li>
					<li>
						Download DXVK 1.10.3 if no Vulkan 1.3 support is detected
					</li>
					<li>
						Fetch steam deck comaptibility
					</li>
				</ul>
				<p>
					BugFixes
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Update Steam runtime to Sniper
					</li>
					<li>
						Favourites layout
					</li>
					<li>
						Show correct number of gamecards in recently played
					</li>
					<li>
						Don't add shortcut for DLCs. Fix adding sideload app shortcuts
					</li>
					<li>
						Fix not being possible to change the default installation path
					</li>
					<li>
						Speed up the disabling of DXVK and VKD3D
					</li>
					<li>
						Several other fixes and improvements
					</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
	</releases>
</component>
